beingfrugalandmakingitwork.com 2012-12-21

# Being Frugal and Making It Work: Disclaimer/Privacy Policy

**Disclosure Policy:**  
  
This policy is valid from October 1, 2010  
  
This blog is a personal blog written and edited by me. For questions about this blog, please **[contact me](http://www.beingfrugalandmakingitwork.com/p/contact-me.html)**.  
  
This blog accepts cash advertising, sponsorships, and paid topic insertions.  We will also accept and keep free products (full size, new), services, travel, event tickets, and other forms of compensation from companies and organizations.  
  
This blog abides by word of mouth marketing standards. We believe in honesty of relationship, opinion and identity. The compensation received may influence the advertising content, topics or posts made in this blog. That content, advertising space or post will be clearly identified as paid or sponsored content.  
  
The owner(s) of this blog is not compensated to provide opinion on products, services, websites and various other topics. The views and opinions expressed on this blog are purely the blog owners. If we claim or appear to be experts on a certain topic or product or service area, we will only endorse products or services that we believe, based on our expertise, are worthy of such endorsement. Any product claim, statistic, quote or other representation about a product or service should be verified with the manufacturer or provider.  
  
This blog does not contain any content which might present a conflict of interest.   

_To get your own policy, go to_[ _http://www.disclosurepolicy.org_](http://www.disclosurepolicy.org/)  

**Privacy Policy:**  

**What information do we collect?**   
  
We collect information from you when you respond to a survey.   
  
When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.  
  
**What do we use your information for?**   
  
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:   
  
; To personalize your experience  
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)  
  
; To improve our website  
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)  
  
; To process transactions

> Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.

; To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature  

; To send periodic emails

> The email address you provide for order processing, will only be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order.

**Do we use cookies?**   
  
We do not use cookies.  
  
**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**   
  
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.  
  
**Third party links**   
  
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.  
  
**Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**   
  
We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.  
  
**Terms and Conditions**   
  
Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at <http://www.beingfrugalandmakingitwork.com/p/disclosure-policy.html>  
  
**Your Consent**   
  
By using our site, you consent to our [privacy policy](http://www.freeprivacypolicy.com/).  
  
**Changes to our Privacy Policy**   
  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will update the Privacy Policy modification date below.   
  
This policy was last modified on 9/12/2012
